[{"answer": "Yes, you know, I think if you are a Democrat, you take a look at these numbers, you say gee, President Obama is still up 11 points in the state by those who voted.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "But what lessons should we take from tonight's Republican win in this recall election looking ahead to November?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "-- guards in particular -- I can hear it now, actually.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Can you hear that?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Well, the first thing is it emerges very quickly that people do care.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "When people say why should we care that the Queen is having her 60th anniversary celebration, what do you say?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "(Inaudible) on the carriage.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "Brooke?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Oh, it was fantastic.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 117, "question": "The Queen and Prince Charles made that great speech, what did it feel like to be there?", "qSentId": 116}, {"answer": "Oh, they'll have a gilt-edged umbrella, I would imagine.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 127, "question": "-- the Queen be holding an umbrella in such a carriage?", "qSentId": 126}, {"answer": "He was actually carriage driving --", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 133, "question": "Was he really?", "qSentId": 132}, {"answer": "At the age of 90, 91 on Sunday.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "At the age of 90?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "I think she represents something that is constant in a changing world.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Why is she so revered and not just in this country but around the world?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "I've just never -- I've never, ever seen it.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "(Inaudible), aren't you, Brooke?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "We do.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 211, "question": "We do, don't we?", "qSentId": 210}, {"answer": "Because her husband isn't here.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "How do you know?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Because it's all about the line of succession.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Chatting.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "Out of interest, when you're all standing behind the curtains waiting to come out, what are you all doing?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Lots of family gossip.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "About -- about what?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "And drinking homemade lemon refresher.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "About what?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Lemon refresher?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "I feel like they've been energized these last four days to a new level again.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "I think it's just a great endorsement for the royal family, isn't it?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "No, totally false assumption.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "That's not going to happen, is it?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Immense pride to be sitting here.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Gut reaction to what we just saw?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Very, very emotional.", "docId": "120605pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Wasn't it?", "qSentId": 447}]